So router agents are things where you have an agent that essentially uses a router
that sits in front of it and calls other functions or potentially other agents.
It can be workflows. It can be agents. It can be whatever.
And the router that sits in front of it doesn't have to be an agent.
It can be an if-then statement, an algorithm, whatever.
And then you evolve from router agents into these things called orchestration agents.
So orchestration agents are, essentially, like—you can think about the router. Router agents...
...go one way. With orchestration agents, you come into the router,
or in this case the orchestrator, and it can get information back from the agents.
They can kind of work like this.
So it goes back and forth between the different things and accomplishes more complex tasks.